[
    {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "Question 1. Which one has the largest fangs?",
        "answer": "Gaboon Viper",
        "choices": [
            "King Cobra",
            "Pit Viper",
            "Gaboon Viper",
            "Western Diamondback RattleSnake"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "Question 2. Which is the biggest land carnivore?",
        "answer": "Polar Bear",
        "choices": [
            "Walrus",
            "Polar Bear",
            "Grisley Bear",
            "Elephant Seal"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Question 3. Which of the following is found only in Africa?",
        "answer": "Grey Parrot",
        "choices": [
            "Toucan",
            "Macaw",
            "Grey Parrot",
            "Magpie"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "Question 4. Which of the following is exclusively an herbivore?",
        "answer": "Ibex",
        "choices": [
            "Hippopotamus",
            "Aardvark",
            "Ibex",
            "Ibis"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "Question 5. Which is the biggest species of tiger?",
        "answer": "Siberian Tiger",
        "choices": [
            "Siberian Tiger",
            "Royal Bengal Tiger",
            "Javan Tiger",
            "Sumatran Tiger"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "Question 6. Which one has the second highest biting force?",
        "answer": "Turtle",
        "choices": [
            "Hyena",
            "Turtle",
            "Crocodile",
            "Lion"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Question 7. Which of the following has the highest wingspan?",
        "answer": "Wandering Albatross",
        "choices": [
            "African Condor",
            "Wandering Albatross",
            "Golden Eagle",
            "Harpy Eagle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "Question 8. Which one of the following primarily eats fish?",
        "answer": "Osprey",
        "choices": [
            "Osprey",
            "Bald Eagle",
            "Peregrene Falcon",
            "Swift"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "Question 9. Which mammal has the most neck vertebrae?",
        "answer": "Sloth",
        "choices": [
            "Manatee",
            "Sloth",
            "Giraffe",
            "Elephant"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Question 10. Which one of them is the fastest?",
        "answer": "Sailfish",
        "choices": [
            "Sailfish",
            "Swordfish",
            "Sawfish",
            "Marlin"
        ]
    }
]
